Guide to the Boniface I. Obichere papers, 1959-1996
Obichere, Boniface I. papers, 1959-1996
- Series III. Students and Teaching
  - Class Files
    - History 201N, Topics in African History
      - History 201N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1984-1988 (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - History 201N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1992, 1995, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - History 201N: Class rosters, grade lists, course evaluations [RESTRICTED], 1984-1995 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - History 230N, Advanced Historiography: Africa
      - History 230N: Syllabi and reading lists, 1967-1974 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - History 230N: Term paper topics and proposals, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - History 230N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1967 (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - History 230N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - History 230N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1971 (Box 8, Folder 29-30)
      - History 230N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - History 230N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - History 230N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - History 230N: Class lists, grade petition [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - History 240N, States, Kingdoms and Empires in 19th Century West Africa
      - History 240N: Syllabi, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - History 240N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - History 240N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - History 240N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - History 240N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      - History 240N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      - History 240N: Student papers [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - History 240N: Class list, enrollment/registration cards [RESTRICTED], 1968, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - History 265B, Seminar in African History
      - History 265B: Syllabi, term paper topics, 1969-1976, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 32)
      - History 265B: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - History 265B: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1970 (Box 9, Folder 8-9)
      - History 265B: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 9, Folder 10-12)
      - History 265B: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - History 265B: Class rosters [RESTRICTED], 1972, 1974, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - History 275, Introduction to the Professional Study of African History
      - History 275: Syllabi, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 33)
      - History 275: Class roster [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - History 278
      - History 278: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - History 278: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1994, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - History 290, Afro-American Studies
      - History 290: Syllabi, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
      - History 290: Student questionaires, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - History 375, Teaching practicum
      - History 375: Class rosters [RESTRICTED], 1995-1996 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - History 406, Problems of Nation Building in Africa Since Independence
      - History 406: Syllabus, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - History 491
      - History 491: Test questions, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - History 491: Grade list [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - History 501: Advanced Historiography: Africa
      - History 501: Syllabus, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - History 501: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - History 596, Directed Studies
      - History 596: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1974-1995, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - History 596: Class rosters [RESTRICTED], 1972-1995 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - History 597, Directed Studies for the Graduate Exam
      - History 597: Test questions, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - History 597: Class rosters [RESTRICTED], 1972-1995 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - History 599, Doctoral Research and Writing
      - History 599: Class rosters [RESTRICTED], 1974-1988 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - PhD and Master's exams: Test questions, 1979-1996, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Obichere's classes: Unidentified syllabi, test questions, handouts, 1987, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Obichere's classes: Student papers/tests for unidentified classes [RESTRICTED], 1969-1995 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Obichere's classes: Student papers/tests for unidentified classes [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 9, Folder 21-22)
    - Obichere's classes: Grades and exam reviews for unidentified classes [RESTRICTED] (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Classes by other professors: Syllabi, test questions, 1968-1996, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Grade book [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Obichere teaching schedules, 1972, 1984, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - African Studies graduate student lists and an inventory of their papers, 1973, 1983, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Student files
    - Students: A [RESTRICTED], 1969-1996, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Students: Achebe, Nwando [RESTRICTED], 1994-1996 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Students: Ahanotu, Austin Metumara [RESTRICTED], 1968-1984 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Students: Aidoo, Agnes [RESTRICTED], 1973-1984, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Students: Allyn, David Edley [RESTRICTED], 1969-1979 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Students: Allyn, David Edley: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 9, Folder 28-29)
    - Students: Amankulor, James Ndukaku [RESTRICTED], 1973-1975 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Students: Aniebo, Ifeanyichukwu [RESTRICTED], 1978-1987 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Students: Aniebo, Ifeanyichukwu: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Students: B [RESTRICTED], 1968-1992 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Students: Barrows, Leland C. [RESTRICTED], 1975, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Students: Barrow, Leland C.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 10, Folder 1-9)
    - Students: Bender, Gerald J. [RESTRICTED], 1965, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Students: Benson, Angela [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Students: Bingen, R. James [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Students: Bobo, Benjamin F. [RESTRICTED], 1972-1983 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Students: Bogen, Marjorie R. [RESTRICTED], 1971, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Students: Bogen, Marjorie R. [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Students: Bogen, Marjorie R. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Students: Bolton, Percy E. [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Students: Booth, Bernard F. [RESTRICTED], 1968, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Students: Borgati, Jean M. [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Students: Bouteba, Paul M. [RESTRICTED], 1991-1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Students: C [RESTRICTED], 1968-1996 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Students: Campbell, Stephanie [RESTRICTED], 1986 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Students: Chamberlin, Christopher [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Students: Chillis, Donald R. [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Students: Chonco, Seshi V. [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Students: D [RESTRICTED], 1968-1996 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Students: Daniels, Darlene [RESTRICTED], 1984-1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Students: DeCorse, Christopher R.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1989 (Box 10, Folder 20-22)
    - Students: Dillard, Mary E. [RESTRICTED], 1994, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Students: Downs, Patricia M. [RESTRICTED], 1975-1984 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Students: Durousseau, Patricia [RESTRICTED], 1973, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Students: Durousseau, Patricia: Master's papers [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Students: E [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Students: Eaton, William O. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1991, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Students: Eaton, William O.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Students: Emereuwaonu, Ernest U. [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Students: Estep, Siri Gian Singh [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Students: F [RESTRICTED], 1968-1996 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Students: Fletcher, Andria: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 10, Folder 29-31)
    - Students: Fletcher, Mikelle [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Students: G [RESTRICTED], 1969-1990 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Students: Gaston, Jessie Ruth [RESTRICTED], 1974-1985, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Students: Gatlin, Darryle [RESTRICTED], 1985-1989, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Students: Gilkesson, Florence L. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Students: Godsey, Larry: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 2-3)
    - Students: Gulliksen, Gail J. [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Students: H [RESTRICTED], 1971-1995 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Students: Haar, Stephan G. [RESTRICTED], 1975, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Students: Harmon, Stephen A. [RESTRICTED], 1982-1993, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Students: Haskett, Norman [RESTRICTED], 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Students: Hawkins, Joye B. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Students: Hawkins, Joye B.: Master's papers [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Students: Holloway, Joseph E. [RESTRICTED], 1973-1987 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Students: Holloway, Joseph E.: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Students: Holloway, Joseph E.: Student papers [RESTRICTED], 1974, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Students: Holloway, Joseph E.: Student papers [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Students: Horne, David L. [RESTRICTED], 1975-1977, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Students: Horton, Christian D. [RESTRICTED], 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Students: Horton, Christian D.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1979 (Box 11, Folder 14-16)
    - Students: Horton, Christian D.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Students: I-J [RESTRICTED], 1975-1994 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Students: Johnson, LeRoy-Ronald [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Students: Jones, Kimberly F.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1995 (Box 11, Folder 20-22)
    - Students: Jones, Solomon [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Students: K [RESTRICTED], 1972-1996 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Students: Kajangu, Kykosa [RESTRICTED], 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Students: Khaemba, Maurice P. [RESTRICTED], 1968-1974, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Students: Kimenyi, Alexandre [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Students: King, James R. [RESTRICTED], 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Students: Kinner, Joseph G.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 11, Folder 27-29)
    - Students: Koon, Thomas G. [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Students: L [RESTRICTED], 1973-1996 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Students: Lee, Anthony A. [RESTRICTED], 1973, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Students: Lian, Jin [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Students: Lord, Carol [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Students: Lynn, Kwaku E. [RESTRICTED], 1984-1989, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Students: Lynn, Kwaku E.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 11, Folder 36-37)
    - Students: M [RESTRICTED], 1968-1996 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Students: Maddox, Jeanne L. [RESTRICTED], 1972-1976, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Students: Mativo, Kyalo W. [RESTRICTED], 1972-1988, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Students: Mativo, Kyalo W. [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
    - Students: McLeod, Wilma [RESTRICTED], 1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Students: N [RESTRICTED], 1968-1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Students: Ngu, Joseph N. [RESTRICTED], 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Students: Nwacukwu, Celestine C. [RESTRICTED], 1972, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Students: Nwankwo, Godson O. [RESTRICTED], 1979-1986, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Students: Nwankwo, Nkeonye C. [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Students: O [RESTRICTED], 1969-1985 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Students: Ogike, Aley U. [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Students: Okihiro, Gary Y. [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Students: Okoth, Pontian G.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11-13)
    - Students: Okwesa, Fidelma U. [RESTRICTED], 1972, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Students: Okwu, Edward C. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Students: O'Sullivan, John M. [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Students: O'Sullivan, John M. [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Students: P [RESTRICTED], 1968-1995 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Students: Phillips, John E. [RESTRICTED], 1982-1987, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Students: Phillips, John E.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 13, Folder 18-20)
    - Students: Pickett, Shirley N. [RESTRICTED], 1973-1978 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Students: Pickett, Shirley N.: Master's papers [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Students: Pirio, Gregory R. [RESTRICTED], 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Students: Powell, Betty P. [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Students: R [RESTRICTED], 1968-1988 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Students: Radcliffe, Kendahl [RESTRICTED], 1992-1996 (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Students: Ralston, Richard D. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Students: Rose, Victoria [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Students: S [RESTRICTED], 1968-1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Students: Saether, Gjermund [RESTRICTED] (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Students: Saxon, Douglas E. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Students: Saxon, Douglas E.: Master's papers [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Students: Saxon, Douglas E.: Drafts [RESTRICTED] (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Students: Siegel, Eric [RESTRICTED], 1968-1976 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Students: Ssali, Mike [RESTRICTED], 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Students: Stamps, Terry L. [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Students: Sweeny, Paul [RESTRICTED], 1969-1972 (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Students: Syas, Stacy [RESTRICTED], 1991 (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Students: T [RESTRICTED], 1968-1995 (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Students: Taylor, Antoine [RESTRICTED], 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Students: Thompson, Brian P. [RESTRICTED], 1994-1995 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Students: U, V, W, Y [RESTRICTED], 1968-1996 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Students: Udoh, Claton T. [RESTRICTED], 1972-1975 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Students: Ukwuoma, Cornelius C.O. [RESTRICTED], 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Students: Ward, Jennifer C. [RESTRICTED], 1971-1976 (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - Students: Ward, Jennifer C.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 13, Folder 41-43)
    - Students: Ward, Jennifer C.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1976 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Students: Ward, Jennifer C.: Book manuscript [RESTRICTED], 1978 (Box 14, Folder 2-4)
    - Students: Williams, Gene [RESTRICTED], 1975-1979 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Students: Williams, Joy E. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Students: Williams, Joy E.: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Students: Williams, Paul A. [RESTRICTED], 1972-1978 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Students: Yoder, Paul Stanley [RESTRICTED], 1973-1976 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Students: Young, Sherilynn J. [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Students: Yusuf, Ore [RESTRICTED], 1984 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Students: Yusuf, Ore: Dissertation draft [RESTRICTED] (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Students: Zimmer, Donald A. [RESTRICTED], 1987-1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Student recommendations (combined) [RESTRICTED], 1969 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Professional Reviews and Recommendations
    - Reviews/Recommendations: A [RESTRICTED], 1973-1986 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Adjaye, Joseph [RESTRICTED], 1985-1989 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Anderson, Perry [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: B-D [RESTRICTED], 1972-1994 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Brooks, George E. [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Brown, Lloyd [RESTRICTED], 1974 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Reveiws/Recommendations: David, Wilfred L. [RESTRICTED], 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Davis, Richard H. Jr. [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Reviews/Recommendaitons: Dogbe, Samuel K. [RESTRICTED], 1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: E-G [RESTRICTED], 1975, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Egboh, Edmund O. [RESTRICTED], 1985 (Box 12, Folder 14-16)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Ekechi, Felix K. [RESTRICTED], 1972-1977 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Eleazu, Uma O. [RESTRICTED], 1973-1974 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Esedebe, Peter O. [RESTRICTED], 1974, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Hamner, William [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Hewitt, Mary Jane [RESTRICTED], 1973 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: J-N [RESTRICTED], 1972-1996 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Jackson, Kennell Jr. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1976 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Lofchie, Kay [RESTRICTED], 1975 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Long, Jerome [RESTRICTED], 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Nair, Kannan Kutty [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: O-Z [RESTRICTED], 1973-1987 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Ogbu, John U. [RESTRICTED], 1974-1975 (Box 14, Folder 27-28)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Ogbu, John U. [RESTRICTED], 1977 (Box 14, Folder 29-31)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Onwuka, Uga [RESTRICTED], 1972-1975 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Osoba, S.O. [RESTRICTED], 1984, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 21-24)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Sherman, Fred [RESTRICTED], 1988 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Reviews/Recommendations: Thompson, Vincent B. [RESTRICTED], 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Resumes/C.V.'s: A [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Resumes/C.V.'s: B [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Resumes/C.V.'s: C-E [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Resumes/C.V.'s: F-I [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Resumes/C.V.'s: J-M [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Resumes/C.V.'s: N-O [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Resumes/C.V's: P-R [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Resumes/C.V.'s: S-T [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Resumes/C.V.'s: U-W [RESTRICTED], n.d. (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Series IV. Written Works, Speeches, and Publications
  - Obichere's Works
    - "Africa and the International System, 1919-1939" (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - African States and the Military: Past and Present, editor, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - African States and the Military: Aidoo, Agnes A., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - African States and the Military: Akintoye, S.A., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - African States and the Military: Bennett, Valerie Plave, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - African States and the Military: Chanaiwa, David, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - African States and the Military: Ekechi, Felix, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - African States and the Military: Gutteridge, William, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - African States and the Military: Lemarchand, René, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - African States and the Military: Marcus, Harold G., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - African States and the Military: Maroukis, Thomas C., 1975-1988 (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - African States and the Military: Oloruntimehin, B. Olatunji, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - African States and the Military: Ryan, Selwyn, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - African States and the Military: Ukpabi, S.C., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - African States and the Military: Uzoigwe, G.N., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - African States and the Military: Welch, Claude E., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - "African States and the South African Problem", 1986 (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - Afro-American History: New Perspectives and Dimensions, editor (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - Afro-American History: Photocopied articles, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Afro-American History: Manuscript, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 56-57)
    - Afro-American History: Edited manuscript, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 58-61)
    - "Afro-Americans in Africa: Recent Experiences," in Black Homeland/Black Diaspora: Cross Currents of the African Relationship, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - "L'Alliance Manquée: Relations Between West African Rulers in the Late Nineteenth Century", n.d. (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - "American Diplomacy in Africa: Problems and Prospects," in Pan African Journal, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - "Benin City and the Royal Patronage of the Arts," in Images of Power: The Royal Court Art of Benin, edited by Flora S. Kaplan; also presented as "Royal Patronage of the Arts in the Precolonial Kingdom of Benin" at the National Museum, Benin City, 1981, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - "Biafra: An African Experiment in Nation Building", n.d. (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - "Black Power and Black Magic in Haitian Politics: Dr. Francois Duvalier, 1957-1971," in Pan-African Journal, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - "Black Studies in the United States of America," in Universitas, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - Book reviews, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - "Change and Innovation in the Administration of the Kingdom of Dahomey" in Journal of African Studies (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - "Collective Security in Contemporary Africa" in The Legon Observor, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - "Continuity and Change in Zimbabwe," in Southern Africa in the 1980s, edited by Olajide Aliko et al., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - Crisis in Zimbabwe, editor, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - "Education for National Liberation in Africa", n.d. (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - "Education Ordinances and Colonial Education Policy in Senegal" in Black Academy Review, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - "The Factor in the Establishment of French Authority in West Africa, 1880-1904" in Britain and France in Africa, edited by Professor Gifford and William Rogert Louis, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - Foreward for Grace L. Chavis-Butler, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa, editor, 1972-1975 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa: D'Azevedo, Warren L., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa: Eleazu, Uma O., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa: Griffeth, Robert R., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa: Johnson, G. Wesley, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa: McCall, Daniel F., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa: Newbury, Colin W., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa: Ottenberg, Simon, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa: Phillips, Earl, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - The Formation and Development of States in West Africa: Williams, Dalbert A., 1973 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "Hunger in Africa and the Problems of Independence", 1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - "Imo State University in the Context of Higher Education in Nigeria," Imo State University convocation lecture, Jan. 23, 1986 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Introduction to the Journal of African Studies, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 29)